Carla: Well, you know what you have to do.
You should apologize.
Ben: I have apologized!
But she doesn’t listen to me.
Carla: Izzy’s angry.
Of course she’s angry.
She probably thinks that you don’t trust her.
Ben: I trust her! Of course I trust her.
Emma: Do you trust her?
Ben: Yes.
Nothing happened between her and Max.
Emma: But do you believe her?
Ben: Yeah!
Emma: Or do you just want to believe her?
Ben: What do you mean?
Emma: You think she’s going to break up with you.
That she might be happier without you.
Ben: No, I don’t.
Emma: Or maybe, just maybe, you think you might be happier without her.
Ben: I…no, that’s not true.
I want to stay with her.
Emma: Then you’ll have to change.
But do you want to change?
Ben: No.
Izzy: Ben.
Love is sometimes hard work.
Things don’t always go to plan.
People change.
But it’s always worth it if it’s the right person.
So ask yourself this:
am I the right person?
Ben: I don’t know anymore.